[
  {
    "day": "January 1st",
    "question": "What is your number one New Years resolution?",
    "answer": "Getting in shape really - I want to look awesome for Forest and Im already starting to get there. Watch the weight, eat healthier, and stick to working out as often as I can. Trying new foods, being more present, write better, keep the anger down.",
    "additional": "Started the New Year off right - K took the kids to Bryans and I stayed home for some relaxation. 3 hours of tripping, listening to music, and enjoying myself. Best trip yet I think."
  },
  {
    "day": "January 2nd",
    "question": "What do you want to be different about this year?",
    "answer": "I want to be calmer, more collected, to communicate better. I want to get in shape, and eat better. Nothing major, just lead a better life",
    "additional": "Started on the trooper helmets in between meetings. Back to work, then homemade pizza! Nice!"
  },
  {
    "day": "January 3rd",
    "question": "What did you learn from last year?",
    "answer": "That I can actually stick to resolutions. I can have healthy boundaries and speak up for myself. I can take time for myself. To be present. I learned where I unfortunately got a lot of my mental health behaviors.",
    "additional": "Cut out pieces for the trooper helmet, worked, worked out, productive day."
  },
  {
    "day": "January 4th",
    "question": "What mistake do you vow to never make again?",
    "answer": "It sounds like a cop-out but I don't vow to never make any specific mistake again. I'm human, I'm going to make mistakes, and I'd like to think I've made it this far in life without making such egregious mistakes that I couldn't repeat. I mean there's a lot of stuff from High School that I'd do differently, but c'mon, who wouldn't.",
    "additional": "Working out yesterday strained something in my arm. Hurt like hell all day but feeling better now. Super tired from staying up too late last night."
  },
  {
    "day": "January 5th",
    "question": "What is something you've been procrastinating that you can't put off?",
    "answer": "Christmas cards. Its January and I still haven't got them out. At least I printed off the photos, and addressed the envelopes, but I still need to get everything done.",
    "additional": "Work, then therapy, home and chillin with Alison."
  },
  {
    "day": "January 6th",
    "question": "What do you need to make more time for?",
    "answer": "Me time. Karen and I have been working on this for ever. I don't get enough",
    "additional": "Super busy day but not bad. I actually did get some me time while Kendall took the girls to a birthday party. I figured out the surround sound issue with the PSVR in the basement, so next time I trip its going to be fucking amazing. Took the girls sledding, then Alison and I went to the Arboretum lights with Dad and Mary before hading to BDs for dinner."
  },
  {
    "day": "January 7th",
    "question": "How do you feel about second chances?",
    "answer": "For some situations absolutely, but look at intent. If you make a mistake, not a big deal, fix it and move on. But if the intent was bad, I don't like forgive and forget unless you have a good conversation about consequences of breaking trust again.",
    "additional": "Double play date, yikes a busy day. Sledding at Autumn Creek with Oliver, Cordelia, Alison, and Emma, then back to the house for hot chocolate. Got a roaring fire going, and then dinner and bedtime routine. "
  },
  {
    "day": "January 8th",
    "question": "What do you think it will take to make your dreams come true?",
    "answer": "I'm 42, so my dreams are much more grounded in reality right now. I think the bike trip and EF are the biggest things I am looking forward to, and at least for the trip I need to get in good cardio shape. For EF I want to drop a few pounds and get some more definition, which means dedication to a daily workout routine",
    "additional": "Monday, back to work. Nothing special, just work, dinner, kids to bed, then pass out"
  },
  {
    "day": "January 9th",
    "question": "What gets you up in the morning?",
    "answer": "Wow, I should be more optimistic than this, but my first thought was 'Kids', or 'Cats'. I don't get to sleep in, but thats not what the question is. I guess just providing for the family, taking care of things, and trying to be responsible",
    "additional": "Snow-day Tuesday. Was supposed to get 6&quot; or so but I think we got 2 or 3, nothing too bad, was really pretty most of the afternoon though."
  },
  {
    "day": "January 10th",
    "question": "My favorite way to start the day is...",
    "answer": "Quiet time in my office, breakfast, Wordle, and just focusing on what needs to get done.",
    "additional": "Nothing spectacular. Work, taking care of Emma while Alison had art and therapy, then Giordannos and Uno with K"
  },
  {
    "day": "January 11th",
    "question": "What do you count on most in your life right now",
    "answer": "My job. 12 years and counting. Brian got laid off before Thanksgiving and still hasn't found anything. Im holding on to this shit for as long as I can. I get paid a decent amount and I like it so I'm not moving on anytime soon",
    "additional": "Thursday - another day of work, Kendall did therapy and then came home. Tired. So very tired."
  },
  {
    "day": "January 12th",
    "question": "What have you recently had a revalation about?",
    "answer": "A quote about perfectionism. It's not about trying to be perfect, its about seeing the imperfections way too easily. Woof that hits",
    "additional": "Shit Friday. Huge snowstorm overnight, too much for the snow blower. Thankfully Duane helped out. Stayed home all day.Therapy not going well, just disagreeing with Karen. "
  },
  {
    "day": "January 13th",
    "question": "What are you looking forward to?",
    "answer": "Well I think my bike trip isn't going to happen, but Electric Forest still has me excited - working my ass off to get in shape and hopefully look fucking amazing. Plus getting K to let loose will be fuuuuuuuucking amazing.",
    "additional": "Saturday - just chilled at home as temperatures plummeted, kendall went out with Sunni so I hung out with the girls"
  },
  {
    "day": "January 14th",
    "question": "Whats missing from life right now?",
    "answer": "Me time. I don't have any. Kendall had a moms night with Sunny on Saturday, Danielle came over yesterday, and she's at the gym now. I didn't get time for Therapy on Friday, my Tuesday 'me night' didn't happen because of the snow, essentially this year so far I've had a few hours on New Years Day to myself, and thats it.",
    "additional": "Frigid Sunday at home - lots of games, reading, a fire in the fireplace, then Danielle came over for dinner. I passed out after getting the girls down. "
  },
  {
    "day": "January 15th",
    "question": "I am super passionate about...",
    "answer": "Not much these days. No time for photography, no time for making, no time for video games, you get the point... Man this year started off well but January is pretty rough so far",
    "additional": "Monday, MLK day. K's cousin Kristi came over and had lunch. I forgot how loud the Wilcox's are. I snuck in a nap later, but then had to get both girls down. Pizza and games with K after the girls were asleep."
  },
  {
    "day": "January 16th",
    "question": "What's the newest thing you've tried?",
    "answer": "Hummus. Well, thats part of my not so New Years resolution. It was fine, nothing to write home about.",
    "additional": "Tuesday quiet work day, then went to Disc Replay for some me time, nothing exciting."
  },
  {
    "day": "January 17th",
    "question": "What is the biggest question you've asked yourself lately?",
    "answer": "How do I get more me time and why, when I get it, does it feel like a waste?",
    "additional": "Wednesday workday, little lunch time trip because the stars aligned, then hung out with Emma while K and A did their Wed. routine."
  },
  {
    "day": "January 18th",
    "question": "I am currently obsessed with...",
    "answer": "Well, I have my stormtrooper helmets in progress, I'm working on my DeAgostini Falcon, and been playing a ton of Stardew Valley",
    "additional": "Just another day. Work, then feed the girls, bedtime routines, then Jersey Mikes and Uno with K"
  },
  {
    "day": "January 19th",
    "question": "What challenges are you currently facing?",
    "answer": "Mostly a lack of sleep. That's impacting everything. Fighting sleep every afternoon despite having the CPAP machine",
    "additional": "Friday work, but Karen cancelled, so I went out shopping. Picked up some things from Spencers and then what a night"
  },
  {
    "day": "January 20th",
    "question": "My favorite splurge or indulgence is...",
    "answer": "Either fun boots or things for K or a little RSO in the evening for a fun trip...",
    "additional": "Not the best Saturday. Chilled in the morning but then volunteered to go grocery shopping which took a few hours between Sams and Walmart. Yuck."
  },
  {
    "day": "January 21st",
    "question": "What book are you currently reading?",
    "answer": "Listening to Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, reading Heart of the Ocean",
    "additional": "Mini date with Kendall. Dropped Alison at Sunnis, then Emma with the rents, then went to brunch and the mall. Nothing exciting"
  },
  {
    "day": "January 22nd",
    "question": "What is weighing heavy on your heart?",
    "answer": "Oof, hard question. Self confidence and lack of personal forgiveness is probably the biggest",
    "additional": "Back to work for a boring Monday. Nothing too exciting. Dinner with fam then bedtime routine."
  },
  {
    "day": "January 23rd",
    "question": "What was the last thing you bought for yourself?",
    "answer": "Well the things from Spencers were for K but really for me, so that counts I guess. Actually for me? My Falcon subscription is monthly so we'll go with that",
    "additional": "Not a bad day - productive. Taxes in the morning, surprise client meeting that went very well, then got some work done. Took girls to Culvers, then pizza with K"
  },
  {
    "day": "January 24th",
    "question": "What gives you a headache just thinking about it?",
    "answer": "Performance reviews at work. The competency matrix and all this nonsense about situations and outcomes. Too complicated",
    "additional": "Really productive work day, banged out some dispatch stories for Kendra, and just generally got shit done. Still dog tired."
  },
  {
    "day": "January 25th",
    "question": "What's been inspiring you lately?",
    "answer": "Frankly not a lot, January has been rough. Im trying to get my ass in shape, so some Instagram accounts I follow help, I want to look good at EF",
    "additional": "Another productive work day. Feeling inspired about the bike trip, need to pull the Flyer upstairs and start getting it cleaned up"
  },
  {
    "day": "January 26th",
    "question": "Sum up in one word what you want out of life.",
    "answer": "Happiness? One word is hard. Peace. Security. Calm. Adventures. See, thats 5 right there...",
    "additional": "Friday with sort of actual me time. K donated blood so I didn't leave till late, but I stopped a few places and didn't get home till much later than usual. Nice"
  },
  {
    "day": "January 27th",
    "question": "Do you feel complete?",
    "answer": "No, I don't think anyone does, do they? There's always more to do, more to learn, more to explore!",
    "additional": "Emma doctor appointment in the morning but then Cousins get together at Dereks. LOUD night, it went okay. Just so loud. Back started hurting from being on that hardwood floor all night."
  },
  {
    "day": "January 28th",
    "question": "What is the biggest goal you're working towards?",
    "answer": "The Grand Tour - riding from Chicago to DC. I really hope I can pull it off. That and getting in better shape for EF",
    "additional": "Productive Sunday. Laundry, cleaning, Emma had a playdate while I did grocery shopping, then made dinner. Worn the fuck out."
  },
  {
    "day": "January 29th",
    "question": "What is the one thing you wish you could have accomplished today?",
    "answer": "Well its morning so I hope to answer some questions about some upcoming client demos, so I still can do that.",
    "additional": "Another shit Monday. Work then K left cause she was in a bad mood, dinner, and Emma was a handful getting to bed"
  },
  {
    "day": "January 30th",
    "question": "When you look in the mirror, what do you see?",
    "answer": "Usually the neck down lol. When I do look I see my tired aging ass, it aint good.",
    "additional": "Not a bad Tuesday to be honest. Quiet time during the day here, then took some me time in the evening and took myself shopping and a burger at Crusade."
  },
  {
    "day": "January 31st",
    "question": "How do you feel about change?",
    "answer": "I typically hate it. I like routines, I eat the same meals at restaurants, I keep things the same in my office, I do the same things quite often. Its comforting. The thought of moving to Michigan makes me want to crawl out of my skin",
    "additional": "Ho hum Wednesday. Worked, then K and I went to therapy with Alison which was okay. Home, dinner routine with Emma, then K and I watched Barbie in the theater."
  },
  {
    "day": "February 1st",
    "question": "What did you have for breakfast this morning?",
    "answer": "Nothing! Again! What am I having for lunch? Probably nothing! Not much in the house and I can't leave. Good times",
    "additional": "Busy ass Thursday. Worked my butt off, shit meeting with Equity because the guy hates truck drivers and apparently SSI while trying to wrangle kids while K was at therapy. Bedtime routine, then finally Jersey Mikes before passing out."
  },
  {
    "day": "February 2nd",
    "question": "Favorite love song?",
    "answer": "Sleepwalk, by Santo &amp; Johnny. Not a love song per-se, but it was our first dance",
    "additional": "Just another Friday. Therapy, then a little bit of window shopping but then right home. Getting excited about my DnD campaign, lots of inspiration."
  },
  {
    "day": "February 3rd",
    "question": "My worst enemy is...",
    "answer": "I don't really have any enemies, I mean, cmon I'm 42. I guess self esteem? My own brain? Thats probably my biggest one",
    "additional": "Took Alison out to the Library and then to Sushi Plus, but then she wasn't feeling so good. Kendall went to Whitney's in the evening so it was a quiet night. Not bad"
  },
  {
    "day": "February 4th",
    "question": "When you woke up this morning who was the first person you thought of?",
    "answer": "Well Alison vomited at midnight, and Pickle was picking at the trash at 4am, so when I woke up at 5:30 I was pretty upset, however I went to check on Alison",
    "additional": "Both the girls were sick, took care of them while K went out for lunch with Jamie, then she did some shopping in the evening."
  },
  {
    "day": "February 5th",
    "question": "When was the last time you did something special for someone?",
    "answer": "The other day, gave K the credit card and sent her on a little adventure. That was fun, although I have to admit it was mostly for me",
    "additional": "Monday - both girls stayed home sick, quiet day"
  },
  {
    "day": "February 6th",
    "question": "Do you have a special someone?",
    "answer": "Yes, my wife and daughters. Not the best question in the world",
    "additional": "Both girls back at school but K started feeling awful when we went to get Alison for a family date, so we headed home. Emma proceeded to have a fever spike, then puke everywhere and have an awful evening. Got calzones for dinner though, so at least there's that."
  },
  {
    "day": "February 7th",
    "question": "How do you feel about cuddling?",
    "answer": "Spooning is the best, easiest way to fall asleep. Its harder when K falls asleep on my chest.",
    "additional": "Emma shockingly woke up happy as a clam, so went back to school. I worked my ass off and I think thats about it"
  },
  {
    "day": "February 8th",
    "question": "Life taught me the biggest lesson when...",
    "answer": "Mom died. What a kick in the teeth. Taught me nothing lasts, try to enjoy what you have when you have it. Can't say that I've stuck with that sentiment completely but I do think about it often.",
    "additional": "Another Thursday but at least K did therapy remote so she wasn't gone all night, although she's getting sick, so bleh"
  },
  {
    "day": "February 9th",
    "question": "My favorite love story is between...",
    "answer": "I used to like Ross and Rachel, but thats much more toxic than I realized when I was 16. Cloud and Aerith? Collins and Angel have the best love song, so does that count?",
    "additional": "Work, therapy, a little window shopping at Fox Valley Mall, then home to play Dokapon with Alison"
  },
  {
    "day": "February 10th",
    "question": "The best kiss I ever had was from...",
    "answer": "My wife, although I don't think I can remember any specific one.",
    "additional": "Kendall is sick so I took care of the girls all day. Library, Culvers, then fun at home before pancakes and bedtime routine."
  },
  {
    "day": "February 11th",
    "question": "...gives me butterflies.",
    "answer": "Antipication of something, like our upcoming date night",
    "additional": "Kendall still sick. Watched the kids all day. Superbowl Sunday, got some pizza from Mike and Denises after the girls went down."
  },
  {
    "day": "February 12th",
    "question": "Describe love in one sentence.",
    "answer": "It may be a cop out, but you can't describe it, its just something that hits you like an atom bomb, you know through and through you'd spend the rest of your days adoring that person, doing anything for them.",
    "additional": "Back to work. Gettin shit done thankfully, well, DnD stuff anyway. I need to buckle back down on actual work."
  },
  {
    "day": "February 13th",
    "question": "What is your idea of romance?",
    "answer": "One on one time, quiet dinners with long conversations, and an enjoyable evening at home afterwards.",
    "additional": "Tax return hit....aaaaaaaand its gone. Well, so is all of our debt, but still. Went out for me time but didnt actually do anything for myself, just got Kendall some tapestries for downstairs, minis for the upcoming game, and valentines stuff for the girls."
  },
  {
    "day": "February 14th",
    "question": "What are your Valentines Day plans?",
    "answer": "Nothing! We're going out Saturday for an activity and then staying at a hotel, but we don't celebrate valentines day specifically",
    "additional": "Day started off shit...literally. Emma had a bad accident at some point during the night and woke us up at 5. Not the best way to start the day"
  },
  {
    "day": "February 15th",
    "question": "Do you kiss and tell?",
    "answer": "Nope! I think the fundamental blocker there is I don't really talk to anyone other than Kendall",
    "additional": "Work, then K went out for therapy and dinner with Bryan."
  },
  {
    "day": "February 16th",
    "question": "What has been your biggest regret recently?",
    "answer": "I think I am sliding back in my self forgiveness and getting angry quickly. I need to work on that.",
    "additional": "Work then therapy for me. After therapy I think I did a tiny bit of shopping but was home pretty quick for games with Alison"
  },
  {
    "day": "February 17th",
    "question": "What has been the best advice you've heard lately?",
    "answer": "Not advice, but the full quote here is much different than the clipped one most people say: Imitation is the sincerest form of flattery that mediocrity can pay to greatness",
    "additional": "Brunch with Bryan and Lindsay, then dropped the kids off at Dads, then hotel stay. First time the RSO didn't kick in."
  },
  {
    "day": "February 18th",
    "question": "Where is your favorite place to shop and what do you love to shop for?",
    "answer": "Physical place would be disc replay and games for myself, but online Demonia for K 100%",
    "additional": "Breakfast with K then got the girls and home to chill"
  },
  {
    "day": "February 19th",
    "question": "My biggest smile happened when...",
    "answer": "Hmm, not sure. Had a pretty good weekend",
    "additional": "Back to work. Not ready for it"
  },
  {
    "day": "February 20th",
    "question": "What would make your day better?",
    "answer": "Just some peace and quiet. People have been asking me a lot lately, its hard to keep up with all the demand.",
    "additional": "Quiet day all things considered. Just working."
  },
  {
    "day": "February 21st",
    "question": "What are you craving this very moment?",
    "answer": "Chocolate. Its been a long time since I've had actual chocolate, like a bar, or a brownie, or a cookie. Being healthy sucks.",
    "additional": "Oops. Okay, forgot about this for about a week. Shit. Get back on the horse. Shit day, another fight with K."
  },
  {
    "day": "February 22nd",
    "question": "If you could take a day for yourself tomorrow, how would you spend it?",
    "answer": "I'd get on my bike and ride. Just take a leisurely ride up to St Charles and back, though probably not that far, I haven't ridden this year except for 2 miles today. But stil...",
    "additional": "Solar panel is here, and I was able to get the bike out!"
  },
  {
    "day": "February 23rd",
    "question": "What was the last movie that made you cry?",
    "answer": "Inside Out probably",
    "additional": "Work, then remote therapy, and mini date night at home with K"
  },
  {
    "day": "February 24th",
    "question": "Do you believe in soulmates?",
    "answer": "No. Seven billion people on the planet, I think its silly that there's one person out there.",
    "additional": "Lazy morning, brunch and a hike before getting the girls. Then a nightmare getting them both to bed"
  },
  {
    "day": "February 25th",
    "question": "Luck or destiny?",
    "answer": "Its a combination of luck and hard work. I don't think anyone is destined to do anything.",
    "additional": "Dropped off Alison at Cordelias, then back to Bryan and Lindsays. The guys took the kids to the park and Colonial while the girls did sushi. Then back to Cordelias for a bit, and back home for a late dinner and bed."
  },
  {
    "day": "February 26th",
    "question": "What is something you're learning to love?",
    "answer": "Myself",
    "additional": "First really nice day outside. Bike ride at lunch, sat in the hammock for a little bit before more work, then outside with Emma for a while."
  },
  {
    "day": "February 27th",
    "question": "Do you have a secret crush you're hiding?",
    "answer": "Seriously? I need a question book for married people. If I did I'd be in trouble lol",
    "additional": "Quiet work day, beautiful weather before the storms hit (supposedly). Got 4 miles in on the bike around the neighborhood, and am feeling it in the legs. Glad Im starting training now."
  },
  {
    "day": "February 28th",
    "question": "Can you keep a secret?",
    "answer": "Yes! Nobody knows that at night I secretly fight crime. Oh wait...",
    "additional": "Work, then Kendall dropped Emma off before grocery shopping, picking up Alison, then back home, and taking her to art. Put both girls down again."
  },
  {
    "day": "February 29th",
    "question": "Error - no question found",
    "answer": "Oops, a 5 year question book didn't account for a leap year? Shocking",
    "additional": "Work, got a ton done, then we did couples therapy which actually went really well. Obviously we don't have any major problems, but improving communication is always a good thing."
  },
  {
    "day": "March 1st",
    "question": "Whats on your mind right now?",
    "answer": "I am so focused on the bike trip its not funny.",
    "additional": "Work, dentist (yuck), shopping, home, and hanging with Alison."
  },
  {
    "day": "March 2nd",
    "question": "Barefoot in grass or sand?",
    "answer": "Sand all the way, but I do go barefoot more than I probably should outside here at home",
    "additional": "Change of plans. Instead of Lilly and Jack coming over, Lilly was sick so Kendall went to watch her while Jack came over here. Low key babysitting night, nothing dramatc thankfully"
  },
  {
    "day": "March 3rd",
    "question": "Favorite place to hang out?",
    "answer": "Home, in the hammock in the back yard with a good book.",
    "additional": "Getting stuff done while the kids play thankfully. Cut the pvc holster for my Insta selfie stick, need to paint and mount to the bike. I have my (probably temp) CHI to DC place mocked up but I don't like that its gray instead of white. Maybe keep looking. Took kids to the park and then to Bryans, not the best afternoon"
  },
  {
    "day": "March 4th",
    "question": "Most relaxing thing you love to do?",
    "answer": "Swing in the hammock with a good book",
    "additional": "Work, took Emma to the park, then took Alison to the park, dinner routine, bed routine. Giordonnos for dinner and Uno with Kendall before a fun little solo trip."
  },
  {
    "day": "March 5th",
    "question": "What do you like most about yourself right now?",
    "answer": "I think I've grown into quite a responsible adult. My credit score just hit 799 last night, which is just unfathomable to me still.",
    "additional": "Work, fighting sleep, then took the girls to the trampoline park and dinner."
  },
  {
    "day": "March 6th",
    "question": "How was yesterday different than today? Was that good or bad?",
    "answer": "Same shit, different day. I've been in this rut all year. The only day I've had off was the 1st. Of fucking January",
    "additional": "Just another day working. Nothing remarkable at all. Alison had therapy and art, so it was a quiet evening here, cooked dinner and then got Emma to bed. Took Alison out for DQ real quick"
  },
  {
    "day": "March 7th",
    "question": "What kind of person are you?",
    "answer": "I hope I am a good person, but mainly I think I am a tired person.",
    "additional": "Work, then Kendall took off for Therapy and dinner, girls routine, totally normal day."
  },
  {
    "day": "March 8th",
    "question": "What recent accomplishment are you most proud of?",
    "answer": "I think mainly therapy and working on myself. I've felt much more level headed as of late, yay",
    "additional": "Work, then therapy and back home, pizza and Uno with Alison before bed."
  },
  {
    "day": "March 9th",
    "question": "Something or someone you have a love/hate relationship with?",
    "answer": "Sugary treats. I used to binge cookies and junk food but for the past year + I've been really good about not gorging myself. Progress!",
    "additional": "Productive morning while K did nothing, fun. Then Lindsay's LotR party. Exhausting day."
  },
  {
    "day": "March 10th",
    "question": "Whats the most recent thing you've wished for?",
    "answer": "Just little things for my bike trip I think - maybe a DJI Mini drone, or camera gear, or the big one is a Catrike Expedition trike.",
    "additional": "DnD prep for next week, K took Emma to a play date, then Alison and I went to Batavia for the library and donuts, back home for pizza and bed routine"
  },
  {
    "day": "March 11th",
    "question": "What is the most spontaneous thing you've done recently?",
    "answer": "Hahhahahahahahahhahahahhahahah yeah no.",
    "additional": "More work, same shit different day. What the fuck do you expect?"
  },
  {
    "day": "March 12th",
    "question": "Do you believe in Angels?",
    "answer": "Nope",
    "additional": "Again - More work, same shit different day. What the fuck do you expect?"
  },
  {
    "day": "March 13th",
    "question": "What do you refuse to spend money on?",
    "answer": "Food delivery if I can help it. Lots of little things like that.",
    "additional": "Just another fucking Wednesday. Shit sleep, work all day, responsibilities until 9:30, then pass out."
  },
  {
    "day": "March 14th",
    "question": "My biggest distraction is...",
    "answer": "Threads, YouTube, other online stuff. Daydreaming about my bike trip. Daydreaming in general.",
    "additional": "Alright, be more optimistic. Well, same shit as yeterday, but with a slightly better outlook. More prep for D&amp;D, Danielle is joining us too. Now its a party"
  },
  {
    "day": "March 15th",
    "question": "Do you count your blessings?",
    "answer": "Ocassionally. Definitely not before, but with therapy I think I am a bit more. I could do it more often.",
    "additional": "Work for a little bit but then off to the dentist and therapy, not the best day, at least its over."
  },
  {
    "day": "March 16th",
    "question": "Edgy or polished?",
    "answer": "What a vague question. Polished I guess? I dunno. I prefer the Millennium Falcon over the Enterprise, so that would be edgy. But I like clean organized things too. Ugh",
    "additional": "Day of cleaning and errands. Ran to Lehans then shopping before coming home and getting prepped for tomorrow."
  },
  {
    "day": "March 17th",
    "question": "How dependable are you?",
    "answer": "Fairly. There's a lot of shit I want to get done that I just dont have the time for",
    "additional": "D&amp;D session 1 with the fam. So exhausted, but at least everyone seemed to enjoy it."
  },
  {
    "day": "March 18th",
    "question": "What is your favorite thing about spring?",
    "answer": "The days where you can get the bike out of the garage and start riding again. ",
    "additional": "Monday, just working, gettin stuff done."
  },
  {
    "day": "March 19th",
    "question": "If you were to put a message in a bottle, what would the first sentence say?",
    "answer": "Wouldn't be a full sentence. Just something inspirational like You Matter.",
    "additional": "Not a bad day, started work, then Kendall took the girls out for lunch while I took a little trip here. Then took the girls to the library for a bit before dinner. Got my first 1 guess in Wordle. Time for a new starting word."
  },
  {
    "day": "March 20th",
    "question": "Favorite place you've travelled so far?",
    "answer": "London was pretty cool, but so was my bike trip to Madison. I think my Grand Tour is going to eclipse them both",
    "additional": "Work, then ripped the cabinets out of the laundry room, dinner with Emma and the bedtime routine."
  },
  {
    "day": "March 21st",
    "question": "What do you think the world needs most right now?",
    "answer": "Dissolution of the cult they call the Republican party.",
    "additional": "Work, dinner, bed. Yep"
  },
  {
    "day": "March 22nd",
    "question": "What is your biggest fear?",
    "answer": "Honestly not sure. I try not to be scared of things, so much is out of my control. Probably something with the girls, like losing one, or something along those lines.",
    "additional": "Light day at work, then off to therapy and the library while K has a quiet evening since Dad and Mary took the girls out"
  },
  {
    "day": "March 23rd",
    "question": "Go out or stay in?",
    "answer": "Oh man, unless its on my bike the answer is always stay in. I don't want to deal with people.",
    "additional": "Morning at the library with the girls, then off to Bryans. Alison, Jack, Bryan, and I met up with the Lillards for a Pokemon walk. Then games back at Bryans while Kendall and Lindsay went to a hotel for a quiet evening."
  },
  {
    "day": "March 24th",
    "question": "What makes you feel homesick?",
    "answer": "Not the best question after years of a pandemic and isolation. I haven't been away from home for more than a day since our Connecticut trip. I haven't been homesick in years.",
    "additional": "Got up and took the girls to the hotel Kendall stayed at for some swimming before heading to Bryans, then back home. Kendall was too tired for anything so I had to take care of both them for the rest of the day"
  },
  {
    "day": "March 25th",
    "question": "Can someone regain your trust after they've lost it?",
    "answer": "Sure, but it takes a lot for them to rebuild it. Plus I'm not around people who've broken my trust to begin with.",
    "additional": "Monday, work, then boom, fight night. Slept on the couch"
  },
  {
    "day": "March 26th",
    "question": "The term 'best friend' means...",
    "answer": "Someone who will drop anything for you, anytime. Complete trust, but will call you out on your bullshit.",
    "additional": "Work, then revisiting the fight. Almost slept on the couch"
  },
  {
    "day": "March 27th",
    "question": "The meanest thing I've done recently is...",
    "answer": "Oh man, this had to come up today. Huge fight with Kendall last night, of course I lost my cool and said Fuck You for the first time. What an asshole.",
    "additional": "So sleep deprived I can barely function."
  },
  {
    "day": "March 28th",
    "question": "How do you handle rejection?",
    "answer": "Not the best, thankfully it doesn't happen much",
    "additional": "Feeling a little better but still horribly sleep deprived. Found my 3d print mount for the bike, might make some adjustments. I need to be more positive about making this trip happen."
  },
  {
    "day": "March 29th",
    "question": "Is anything holding you back?",
    "answer": "Anxiety, depression, anger, guilt, hell yes theres a ton holding me back. Thankfully we're working on it...",
    "additional": "Friday work, then remote therapy, ran some errands afterwards, then the usual routine."
  },
  {
    "day": "March 30th",
    "question": "Favorite break up song?",
    "answer": "Fuck you by Eamon? I dunno, I don't like break up songs, but that one is hilarious.",
    "additional": "Took the girls out to boba, then Geneva Library, and then shopping, giving K some alone time"
  },
  {
    "day": "March 31st",
    "question": "What is your favorite thing to do in a group?",
    "answer": "LAN Party or board game party.",
    "additional": "Easter Sunday - up early with the girls, playing all morning, then over to Dads."
  },
  {
    "day": "April 1st",
    "question": "Do you think people can really change?",
    "answer": "Yes, look at me, I was a filthy gross teenager, now I'm a neurotic neat freak as an adult. Progress?",
    "additional": "Nothing spectacular, work, the usual routine."
  },
  {
    "day": "April 2nd",
    "question": "Morning person or night owl?",
    "answer": "Night owl but not by choice. I wish I could sleep better and more but no, my brain wants to think about things around midnight",
    "additional": "Personal day - Kendall took Emma to the city while Alison was at school so I relaxed."
  },
  {
    "day": "April 3rd",
    "question": "My favorite smell is...",
    "answer": "Hmm, Autumn Wreath from Yankee Candle? Fresh cut grass, that smell when the furnace turns on for the first time in the fall (weird one yes). Coffee even though I hate it.",
    "additional": "Back to work, nothing spectacular. Then getting Emma to bed, then making dinner before passing out at like 10:30"
  },
  {
    "day": "April 4th",
    "question": "Describe your worst overreaction...",
    "answer": "Oh man, I dont know. Lots unfortunately.",
    "additional": "Thursday. No idea what happened"
  },
  {
    "day": "April 5th",
    "question": "Is there life on other planets or an alien presence somewhere?",
    "answer": "Has to be, otherwise, what a waste of space.",
    "additional": "Friday work, then therapy, picked up some Jersey Mikes, and then home"
  },
  {
    "day": "April 6th",
    "question": "Favorite karaoke song you'd actually sing on stage?",
    "answer": "I'd probably rather jump in a fire, but if I had to, it would be the Humpty Dance",
    "additional": "Liams baptism and then hanging out at Dereks till late, then bedtime routine"
  },
  {
    "day": "April 7th",
    "question": "What is something you did that you said you'd never do?",
    "answer": "Edibles",
    "additional": "Sunday eclipse prep. Got everything together while K took the girls out."
  },
  {
    "day": "April 8th",
    "question": "Last promise you broke?",
    "answer": "Not sure",
    "additional": "Eclipse Day - drove down to Alexandria IN with Kendall, the girls, and Danielle. Up and down morning but man, what a show"
  },
  {
    "day": "April 9th",
    "question": "What is somethign that haunts you?",
    "answer": "Well, missing focus on the eclipse Monday is going to hang around my neck for a while.",
    "additional": "Recovery - working in a daze, so tired. At least its a Tuesday so it was quiet. Took the girls to the park after work, then dinner and bed."
  },
  {
    "day": "April 10th",
    "question": "What are you looking forward to right now?",
    "answer": "My bike tour, so so so much. Forest sounds fun and all, but spending 2 weeks on the bike by myself sounds like heaven.",
    "additional": "Work, nothing spectacular. Actually edited my solar eclipse photos and wrote a blog post about it really late."
  },
  {
    "day": "April 11th",
    "question": "What was your most recent victory or success?",
    "answer": "Work stuff maybe? I dunno. Setting more healthy boundaries is probably a better answer.",
    "additional": "Another work day, nothing special again. K went to therapy, then came home. Yup. Thats about it"
  },
  {
    "day": "April 12th",
    "question": "My latest daydream was about...",
    "answer": "The bike tour coming up. Its pretty much all I daydream about",
    "additional": "Friday work, then took Emma to parent night at Peaceful Pathways. Home, dinner, bed."
  },
  {
    "day": "April 13th",
    "question": "What have you had a reoccuring dream about?",
    "answer": "I don't really have reoccuring dreams to be honest. They're always pretty strange and random, very much all over the place, and then I forget them after an hour or so of waking up.",
    "additional": "Kendall took the girls out while I relaxed here most of the day, then she went to Naperville for the evening."
  },
  {
    "day": "April 14th",
    "question": "What was the last lie you told?",
    "answer": "Probably that I was okay with moving?",
    "additional": "Kendall and Alison went to Medieval Times while Emma and I chilled at home. Then we sat in the driveway with Ron and Wendy for a bit before dinner."
  },
  {
    "day": "April 15th",
    "question": "Healthiest habit you have right now?",
    "answer": "Limited junk food, lifting weights and minor exercise each day. Not bad",
    "additional": "Kendall prepping for her procedure which means fun times all around. Worked, took Emma to the park, then took care of the girls for dinner/bed. Finally ate at like 9:45, then bed."
  },
  {
    "day": "April 16th",
    "question": "Worst habit you have right now?",
    "answer": "Sleep - staying up too late, waking up way too early, bad sleep hygiene in general.",
    "additional": "Work in the morning then took Kendall for her procedure. Quick walk around Springbrook Prairie (go back with bike sometime), then to the mall for a bit before picking her back up and going home. Put the girls down and had dinner before making cookies and attempting sleep."
  },
  {
    "day": "April 17th",
    "question": "Are you a good or bad influence on those around you?",
    "answer": "I'd like to say I'm a pretty good influence, although I try not to influence people in general.",
    "additional": "Just another day stuck at home. Patched the bottom of the laundry chute in the laundry room with first round of mud. Progress. Then the usual bedtime routine"
  },
  {
    "day": "April 18th",
    "question": "What did you have for lunch today?",
    "answer": "Vegetable soup. Healthy for once!",
    "additional": "A Thurdsay, nothing spectacular. K went to therapy, I took care of the kids, typical crazy bedtime. Got shit to do before we go out this weekend. Not exactly looking forward to this trip."
  },
  {
    "day": "April 19th",
    "question": "What is something that is widely popular that doesn't appeal to you?",
    "answer": "Alcohol",
    "additional": "Friday work routine, then remote therapy while K dropped off the cats."
  },
  {
    "day": "April 20th",
    "question": "Last person you trolled on social media?",
    "answer": "I don't troll. I post a lot of memes and silly stuff, but I don't like trolls.",
    "additional": "Drove out to Ann Arbor. Pizza dinner at Adam and Danielle's place."
  },
  {
    "day": "April 21st",
    "question": "Funniest person you know?",
    "answer": "Me.",
    "additional": "Kids went with the grandparents while we went around the area. Breakfast in Dexter, a hike at the state park, then house hunting for Bryan and Lindsay, bowling and dinner before crashing back at the lake house"
  },
  {
    "day": "April 22nd",
    "question": "Last person you actually spoke to on the phone?",
    "answer": "Kendall. She's the only one I talk to on the phone.",
    "additional": "Bryan and Lindsay had to work so we took the kids park hopping around Ann Arbor before Passover seder."
  },
  {
    "day": "April 23rd",
    "question": "Who are you waiting on to text you back?",
    "answer": "Nobody. I don't have much of a social life lol",
    "additional": "Drove back home, pretended to work. Grocery shopping, dinner, and then watched a little bit of Westworld before passing out."
  },
  {
    "day": "April 24th",
    "question": "Indoors or outdoors?",
    "answer": "Oh outdoors for sure if possible. Riding the bike, hiking, sitting in the hammock, just getting sunshine is the best",
    "additional": "Work, then K took Ali to therapy and art. Bedtime routine for both girls then dinner and bed. Same shit, different day."
  },
  {
    "day": "April 25th",
    "question": "How do you neglect yourself?",
    "answer": "Wow, yeah, thats a lecture series, not a quick one liner. I don't prioritize myself at all, always putting everyone else first. Its compulsive",
    "additional": "Work, then K went to therapy. Bedtime routine for the girls, then up late getting chores done."
  },
  {
    "day": "April 26th",
    "question": "What do you value the most?",
    "answer": "My family and the home we've created. Not the house itself, the comfortable and safe home.",
    "additional": "Work, then therapy, and a little window shopping while out but really nothing major. Home for pizza and bed."
  },
  {
    "day": "April 27th",
    "question": "When was the last time you dontated something to charity?",
    "answer": "We haul stuff to Goodwill a lot, maybe a month or so.",
    "additional": "Helped B and J pack up and move their stuff to storage, then home, then took the girls to Wolfs Crossing. Dinner, then put Emma down and played Minecraft with Alison"
  },
  {
    "day": "April 28th",
    "question": "What makes someone a good person?",
    "answer": "Trustworthyness, honesty, consistency, and being kind.",
    "additional": "Sunday with Emma - K took Alison to a playdate while Emma and I hung out all day playing games."
  },
  {
    "day": "April 29th",
    "question": "What do you want to learn?",
    "answer": "Hmm, another language? Id like to ride a unicycle for some stupid reason...",
    "additional": "Monday back to work, quiet day thankfully. Normal routine but at least the weather is starting to clear up."
  },
  {
    "day": "April 30th",
    "question": "What gadget are you addicted to?",
    "answer": "My iPhone, 100%. Completely. No question",
    "additional": "Work, was going to do a bike ride but didn't see some calendar stuff, so I had to mow the lawn and watch Emma while I finished work. Then dinner, and bed."
  },
  {
    "day": "May 1st",
    "question": "What are you hoping for?",
    "answer": "I do hope my bike trip works out but man, its really looking like its not going to happen",
    "additional": "Well, bike trip went poof, any plans for the school year are gone. Im in a foul mood. Fuck."
  },
  {
    "day": "May 2nd",
    "question": "What do you take for granted?",
    "answer": "Tons I'm sure. The house, stability, security, my health.",
    "additional": "Feeling better after being sick Wednesdsay. Just the usual Thursday, watched the girls while K went to Therapy."
  },
  {
    "day": "May 3rd",
    "question": "How are you spiritual?",
    "answer": "I'm not really. I want to be a kind person and get through life, but anything beyond that? Not going to figure it out so I'll just try to be a good person.",
    "additional": "Fight Friday. Normal day then K decided to dump shit on me right before therapy which was fun. Good session though, then dinner with the Bowdens"
  },
  {
    "day": "May 4th",
    "question": "Describe today in three words.",
    "answer": "Fun, overdue, intimate",
    "additional": "Played with the girls in the morning and then dropped them off at Dads. Date night - grillin and chillin at home."
  },
  {
    "day": "May 5th",
    "question": "Are you ashamed of anything?",
    "answer": "Yeah, not going to answer that here...",
    "additional": "Date night continued - went out to breakfast, hike at Hoover, then got the kids. Bryan, Lindsay, and the kids came over to play for a bit, then we grilled and did the bedtime routine."
  },
  {
    "day": "May 6th",
    "question": "If you could ban something right now, what would it be?",
    "answer": "Smoking, alcohol, or maybe just DJT off the presidental ballot",
    "additional": "Monday back to work. Quiet day, got a lot done. Can't really complain, although still getting drowsy during the day."
  },
  {
    "day": "May 7th",
    "question": "Best compliment I've recieved lately was...",
    "answer": "No idea. I don't get them often and I really don't like getting them anyway.",
    "additional": "Tuesday work, very quiet. Took Emma to Taekwondo, then bedtime, some tornado sirens, and finally actual bed time."
  },
  {
    "day": "May 8th",
    "question": "It hurts when...",
    "answer": "Passive aggressive comments that K says to nobody in particular when she thinks nobody is listening.",
    "additional": "Wednesday work. Then took Emma to the park, dinner, quick Walmart run, and bed."
  },
  {
    "day": "May 9th",
    "question": "What is the biggest secret you're keeping from someone right now?",
    "answer": "Probably the box of Ritz crackers in the closet. Yeah, I live life on the edge",
    "additional": "Moving day...sort of. I took my office stuff and setup down in the basement. Not super happy about it, but K needs her own space and the basement wouldn't do it for her."
  },
  {
    "day": "May 10th",
    "question": "How is your hair situation today?",
    "answer": "Hahahahhahahahahahahahahhahahahha",
    "additional": "Work, remote therapy, then bedtime routine. In the middle of getting Alison down I poked my head out and realized we could see the northern lights. It was beautiful, but it clouded over in like 5 minutes."
  },
  {
    "day": "May 11th",
    "question": "Describe your confidence using an analogy",
    "answer": "I'm like a sloth. Im not moving until I am sure thats what I want to do.",
    "additional": "BBQ at Centennial Beach with Ks family, then after dropping the kids we went to IKEA and chilled at home, relaxing and eating Giordonnos"
  },
  {
    "day": "May 12th",
    "question": "What is a waste of money but you still buy it anyway?",
    "answer": "Gym memberships, probably Lego if we're being honest, junk food, not too much else.",
    "additional": "Mothers Day - woke up and made pancackes and bacon for K before heading to Lombard to hang with everyone."
  },
  {
    "day": "May 13th",
    "question": "What makes life so complicated?",
    "answer": "Other people. If I was alone it would be so much simpler.",
    "additional": "Work, not a bad Monday, then took Emma to TKD. Home for dinner and bedtime routines, played Minecraft and passed out."
  },
  {
    "day": "May 14th",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "",
    "additional": "Quiet Tuesday, getting shit done. Settling into the basement cave and feeling more comfortable down here. Jersey Mikes for dinner, budget check, and bedtime"
  },
  {
    "day": "May 15th",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "",
    "additional": "Typical Wednesday. Budget stuff, work, K took Ali out for a bit after school, then dinner and too much Minecraft before bed."
  },
  {
    "day": "May 16th",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "",
    "additional": "Thursday. Work, K went to therapy, nothing out of the ordinary"
  },
  {
    "day": "May 17th",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "",
    "additional": "Friday, work, therapy, nice bike ride along the Fox, then home for pizza and Minecraft with Alison"
  },
  {
    "day": "May 18th",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "",
    "additional": "Santas village, back home, then to Carol Stream with Emma to test drive a Jeep which didn't work out. Emma got sick afterwards, so bedtime and passing out after a busy as fuck day."
  },
  {
    "day": "May 19th",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "",
    "additional": "Sunday with the girls. Got the screened in porch door finished and re-hung, looks great. Got the girls to bed and then a little alone time while Kendall babysat Jack and Lilly."
  },
  {
    "day": "May 20th",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "",
    "additional": "Monday back to work. Yuck. Just so so tired. Barely ate, no dinner, passed out."
  },
  {
    "day": "May 21st",
    "question": "",
    "answer": "",
    "additional": "Chill Tuesday. Work, but it was quiet, so laid in bed, then took a break in the hammock for a while. Little more hammock time while Emma and K went to TKD. Throughout the day made some progress on this site, cleaning up some components."
  }
]
